theinnovationenterprise.com 2016-11-07

# The Innovation Enterprise

**Privacy Policy**

CFO Publishing Holdings, Inc. (also referred to in this Privacy Policy as “CFO” “Innovation Enterprise” “ieOnDemand” and with the terms “we,” “us,” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of all those who provide us with their contact information while using our websites, products, events, or services (“you” or “Users”). This policy describes the ways that personally identifiable and anonymous information about our publication subscribers, online and digital media product users, and event registrants is collected, how that information might be shared, and how someone can request changes to the way their personal information is used or shared. A current list of the CFO websites covered by this Privacy Policy (the “Sites”) can be found here.linkedi

Collection of User Details and Information

We may collect personally identifiable and/or anonymous information from you in the course of your use of our websites, products, events, or services (“Services”) as further described in this Privacy Policy. Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you, such as your full name, email address, postal address, telephone number, and fax number. In some cases, you may provide information to us, and in other cases, information about you or your activities on our Services may be automatically collected, as further described below.

We collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us when you subscribe to our magazines (either directly or through another company such as a subscription agency); sign up for email newsletters or promotions; enter a contest; participate in surveys; register for a website, webcast, mobile application, tradeshow or other online or in-person event; or otherwise communicate with us or interact with the Sites. We also may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us.

If you use a credit card to pay for a CFO product or service, we may retain your credit card information in order to renew your account in the event you elect to renew your subscription. When we do retain credit card information, we keep it secure and separate from other demographic information you may have given us.

CFO is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in discussions in our forums or other publicly accessible interactions, or the information that you choose to make public in your member profile. To view or change your member profile, please return to the CFO business site where you registered.

User Details Collected Automatically and Our Uses of Such Information

Like most website operators, we use cookies (small data files stored on your computer by your web browser upon visiting a website), web beacons, and similar technologies to operate our Services efficiently and as intended. Through such technologies we gather information about you, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, mobile device identification number, the sites visited before and after our Site, and about your interactions with our Services, such as the time and date when you viewed a page, which advertisements you have clicked on, and whether you filled out an online form. You may set your browser to block all cookies, including CFO’s, while using our Services (in which case some aspects of the Services may not function properly), or you may set your browser to block third-party cookies and allow first-party cookies, which would allow us (but not third parties) to collect such information while you are on our Sites. In addition, some browsers may allow you to block certain web beacons and similar tracking codes. Please refer to your browser’s documentation if you wish to block some or all cookies, web beacons, and/or similar tools.

We use information gathered through these tools to improve the way our Sites work, for example by employing third-party analytics tools which aggregate anonymized user information to help us better design our Sites, and to enhance the functionality of our Services, for example by remembering preferences or other choices that you make, such as user names, language preferences, and the like. By allowing us to understand how you use our Sites over time, these tools can help us provide you with a better, more relevant online experience. In addition, we may work with third-party advertising companies to target and serve advertising you see on the Services or on third-party sites based on preferences gleaned from such information. For example, we work with a company called Bizo that may, based on your activities on our Sites and/or third party sites in Bizo’s network, serve ads for our or third-party products to you when you visit another site in Bizo’s network. You can review Bizo’s privacy policy at <http://www.bizo.com/privacy_policy>, and can opt-out of Bizo-targeted advertising at<http://www.bizo.com/businessProfessionals/opt_out>.

Third-Party Cookies and Tracking Technologies   

Certain third parties may also employ cookies, web beacons, and/or similar technologies on our Services. Information collected through such third-party tools is gathered directly by such third party, not by CFO, and is subject to such third party's applicable privacy policy. CFO has no control over such third-party tools. These third parties include but are not limited to analytics partners who help us better understand how our users are interacting with our Services and advertising, providers of widgets and other third-party applications that may appear in our Services, ad servers, ad networks, ad agencies, and advertisers. You may visit these third parties' sites to learn more about their privacy practices. In addition, as noted above, you may set your browser to block third-party cookies. Finally, you may visit the industry websites described in the next section to learn more about the privacy practices of a wide range of ad networks and data companies and to exercise certain opt-out options made available there.

Our Sites may include social media features, such as the Facebook button and widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. On some of our Sites, you can log in using sign-in services such as Gravatar or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like these give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Industry Resources Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising

Most of the third-party advertising and data companies with whom we work (including Bizo) are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). NAI offers a tool that will allow you to opt-out of behavioral advertising by NAI members at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>, and the DAA offers a similar opt-out tool regarding behavioral advertising by its members at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. Finally, the DAA manages its Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising (“Self-Regulatory Program”); if you are served an ad by a third party that follows the Self-Regulatory Program, you may click on the Advertising Option Icon (the letter “i” in a blue triangle) or related phrases (e.g., “Why did I get this ad?,” “Interest Based Ads,” or “Ad Choices”) to learn more about applicable behavioral advertising practices and opt-out options.

Use of User Details and Information

We may use your contact information to send you account notices, including subscription renewals or registration confirmation, and to provide you with information about products or services you’ve ordered or which we think may be of interest to you. We may also use your contact information to ask for your input to help in our research about our services, events, or products or to provide you with additional information about the Sites.

We may also send you e-newsletters with targeted, relevant content. Each e-newsletter will provide you with an opportunity to unsubscribe from that particular e-newsletter. Unsubscribing from one newsletter will not affect delivery of other newsletters.

In some cases, we may send you relevant, carefully screened offers from reputable third party businesses or organizations. Many of our customers appreciate receiving these offers because they relate to their business or occupation. However, you will always be able to opt-out of receiving future third party offers.

All promotional and research email messages you receive from us will include an option to opt-out of future email communications from that particular CFO product, service, event, or brand.

User Details and Information We Share with Third Parties

We may provide personally identifiable information to those acting as our agents in providing our products and services, including third-party companies we have employed to provide us with specialized services, including customer service, subscription fulfillment, research, statistical analysis, list cleansing, postal mailings, email and fax deployment, telemarketing, and other information services. In compliance with privacy laws, we also provide our opt-out lists to those third-party companies so that they can be suppressed from the communications those companies send on CFO's behalf.

From time to time our sponsors wish to contact our subscribers and customers who have indicated an interest in the products, services or events provided by such sponsors. If you register for products or services offered by such sponsors or third parties, or for events sponsored in whole or in part by a third party, or otherwise opt-in to permit us to share your personally identifiable information, then you may receive communications directly from such third parties. If you provide information on a co-branded site or while using a co-branded service, you grant us permission to share the information you have provided with that service or site partner. Their use of your information is subject to their privacy policies and we urge you to read those policies and be aware of their privacy practices before registering.

In addition, we may share your contact information with sponsors who appear in a particular e-newsletter of ours if you click on their link in the e-newsletter. If you do NOT wish to have your email address shared with that e-newsletter's sponsors, you will be given an opportunity within the e-newsletter to opt-out.

CFO also shares the information it gathers in a compiled format with advertisers and other partners. The compiled format does not include personally identifiable information.

Quality Control of User Generated Content

CFO uses a third party to monitor user-generated content posted on our websites. When you submit a comment on a CFO website, our third-party service provider, Automattic, may collect, analyze, and store information about you and the content you submit for anti-spam and quality monitoring purposes via its Akismet tool as set forth in Automattic’s privacy policy available at <http://automattic.com/privacy/>.

User Details and Information Transfer

CFO is based in the United States of America. Any information you provide may be stored and maintained in a secure database in the United States or transferred to a secure database outside the United States. By providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

From time to time, we may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf, such as our payment processor or hosting provider, and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

In the case of a change of ownership or a merger involving CFO or any business that is part of CFO, your contact information associated with that business would be one of those transferred assets. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without permission. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to and use of your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number, on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Keeping User Details and Information Secure

We use reasonable precautions, including appropriate technical, administrative, and physical procedures, to protect personal information from loss, misuse, or alteration.

When we contract with other companies to provide us with services, we only share personal information with those that we believe share our commitment to privacy and information security. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. Transmission of information via the Internet can never be completely secure, and all such transmission is at your risk. Due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.

Our Sites may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

Safe Harbor

CFO complies with the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.–Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland

Children's Privacy

CFO's Sites are not intended for use by children, especially those under the age of 13. No one under the age of 13 should provide any personal information or participate in any forums, chats, or online discussions. Minors under the age of 18 are prohibited from making purchases, including subscriptions, on our sites. Please discourage your children from providing any personal information about themselves to anyone in any public discussion areas

California Privacy Rights

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request certain information from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request the above information in relation to any of the Sites, please contact us via email addressed to [privacy@CFO.com](mailto:privacy@CFO.com) or write to us at: CFO, Attn: Customer Service – Privacy, 45 West 45th Street, 12th Floor, New York, NY 10036, with a reference to California Disclosure Information. We will respond to such requests to information access within 30 days following receipt at the e-mail or mailing address stated above. If we receive your request at a different e-mail or mailing address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time, but not to exceed 150 days from the date received. Please note that we are only required to respond to each customer once per calendar year.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date below. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of your personal information, we will attempt to notify you by email of the change. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. If you continue to use our site or services after we have attempted to contact you about material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will assume that you agree to the changes.

Terms of Use

By using any of our Sites, you consent to our use of your contact information as it is outlined in this Privacy Policy.

CFO reserves the right to access and disclose personally identifiable information to comply with applicable laws, lawful government requests and court orders, or to investigate alleged fraud or violations of the Terms of Use of CFO’s Sites.

All users, including those users who access the Sites from a country other than the U.S., agree that the laws of the State of New York shall govern any dispute, including those arising from CFO’s use of personal information or otherwise relating to privacy.

Contact Us

If you wish to update your print magazine subscription contact information, please go to the magazine's home page. If you wish to opt-out of receiving email, faxes, or phone calls from any CFO business, please send an email to [privacy@CFO.com](mailto:privacy@CFO.com) or write/call us at:

CFO Customer Service

45 West 45th Street, 12th Floor

New York, NY 10036

Phone: [](tel:212-459-3004)[212-459-3004](https://www.switch.co/launch?phone=212-459-3004 "Call with Switch.co")

Last Updated: May 15, 2014

 **Innovation Enterprise & ieOnDemand Terms of Service**

By purchasing now, you agree to the following terms. You authorize Innovation Enterprise to store and charge your payment method on file. Your paid account will renew automatically, unless you terminate it, or you notify Innovation Enterprise of your decision to terminate your paid account. You must cancel your subscription before it renews in order to avoid billing of subscription fees for the renewal form to your credit card.

User Agreement

Welcome, and thanks for using Innovation Enterprise, [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) or other Innovation Enterprise services and apps! Innovation Enterprise & ieOnDemand is a subsidiary of CFO Publishing Holdings, Inc. When you use our products and services, you're agreeing to our terms, so please take a few minutes to read over the User Agreement below.

Note: You are entering into a legally binding agreement.

1\. Introduction Last revised on July 15, 2014

We are a online media brand and online learning platform for professionals.

1.1. Purpose

The mission of Innovation Enterprise is to provide the information needs for the next generation of leaders

1.2. Scope and Intent

When you use Innovation Enterprise's services and apps (including [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/)), you are entering into a legal agreement and you agree to all of these terms.

You also agree to our Privacy Policy, which covers how we collect, use, share, and store your personal information.

You agree that by registering on Innovation Enterprise, [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) or by using our websites, including our mobile applications, or any content or information provided as part of the Innovation Enterprise services you are entering into a legally binding agreement with Innovation Enterprise (“we,” “us,” “our,” and “Innovation Enterprise”) based on the terms of this Innovation Enterprise User Agreement and the Innovation Enterprise Privacy Policy, which is hereby incorporated by reference (collectively referred to as the “Agreement”), whether as a registered member on Innovation Enterprise, [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) and/or other Service, as applicable (“Member”), or unregistered user (“Visitor”). If you are using Innovation Enterprise on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you are nevertheless individually bound by this Agreement even if your company has a separate agreement with us. If you do not agree with this Agreement, do NOT click “Submit” and do not access, view, download or otherwise use any Innovation Enterprise webpage, content, information or services. By clicking “Place Order”, “Join Innovation Enterprise”, “Place Order” (on ieondemand.comt) or similar, or by using any Service, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the terms and conditions of this Agreement and that you agree to be bound by all of its provisions. Please note that the Innovation Enterprise User Agreement and Privacy Policy are also collectively referred to as Innovation Enterprise’s “Terms of Service.”

2\. Your Obligations

2.1. Applicable laws and this Agreement

Some promises you make to us in this Agreement:

You will follow the law and Innovation Enterprise’s rules.

You must comply with all applicable laws and this Agreement, as may be amended from time to time with or without advance notice, and the policies and processes explained in the following sections and related webpages:

DOs and DON’Ts;

Complaints Regarding Content Posted on the Innovation Enterprise Website;

Innovation Enterprise’s Privacy Policy; and

Other specific rules for particular Services, such as [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/).

2.2. License and warranty for your submissions to Innovation Enterprise

You still own what you own, but you grant us a license to the content and/or information you provide us.

As between you and Innovation Enterprise, you own the content and information you provide Innovation Enterprise under this Agreement, and may request its deletion at any time, unless you have shared information or content with others and they have not deleted it, or it was copied or stored by other users. Additionally, you grant Innovation Enterprise a nonexclusive, irrevocable, worldwide, perpetual, unlimited, assignable, sublicenseable, fully paid up and royalty-free right to us to copy, prepare derivative works of, improve, distribute, publish, remove, retain, add, process, analyze, use and commercialize, in any way now known or in the future discovered, any information you provide, directly or indirectly to Innovation Enterprise, including, but not limited to, any user generated content, ideas, concepts, techniques and/or data to the services, you submit to Innovation Enterprise, without any further consent, notice and/or compensation to you or to any third parties.

We will respect the choices you make about who gets to see your information and content.

Pursuant to this license, Innovation Enterprise may grant other Members and/or Visitors access and share rights to your content and information in accordance with this Agreement, your settings and degree of connection with them. With respect to your [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) content, you may choose to make it available to Members and Visitors under the Creative Commons license of your choice.

You promise to only provide us information and content that you have the right to give us and you promise that your Innovation Enterprise profile will be truthful.

Any content or information you submit to us is at your own risk of loss. By providing content or information to us, you represent and warrant that you are entitled to submit it and that it is not confidential and not in violation of any law, contractual restrictions or other third party rights (including any intellectual property rights).

It is your responsibility to keep your Innovation Enterprise profile information accurate and updated.

2.3. Service Eligibility

You are eligible to enter into this contract and you are at least our “Minimum Age.”

The information you provide is truthful.

To be eligible to use the Services, you must meet the following criteria and represent and warrant that you: (1) are the “Minimum Age” (defined below) or older; (2) are not currently restricted from the Services, or not otherwise prohibited from having a Innovation Enterprise account, (3) are not a competitor of Innovation Enterprise or are not using the Services for reasons that are in competition with Innovation Enterprise; (4) will only maintain one Innovation Enterprise account (and/or one[ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) account, if applicable) at any given time; (5) will use your real name and only provide accurate information to Innovation Enterprise; (6) have full power and authority to enter into this Agreement and doing so will not violate any other agreement to which you are a party; (7) will not violate any rights of Innovation Enterprise or third party, including intellectual property rights such as copyright or trademark rights; and (8) agree to provide at your cost all equipment, software, mobile access, and internet access necessary to use the Services.

“Minimum Age” means (a) 18 years old for the People’s Republic of China, (b) 16 years old for the Netherlands, (c) 14 years old for the United States, Canada, Germany, Spain, Australia and South Korea, and (d) 13 years old for all other countries. However, if applicable law requires that you must be older than such ages in order for Innovation Enterprise to lawfully provide the Services to you (including the collection, storage and use of your information in accordance with our privacy policy) then the Minimum Age would be such older age. The Services are not designed nor intended for use by children or anyone else under the age of 13.

2.4. Your Membership

You will keep your password a secret.

You will not share an account with anyone else.

You will not copy or transfer any part of the Services.

The profile you create on Innovation Enterprise (including [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/)) will become part of Innovation Enterprise and except for the content and information that you license to us is owned by Innovation Enterprise. However, between you and others, your account belongs to you. You agree to: (1) keep your password secure and confidential; (2) not permit others to use your account; (3) not use other’s accounts; (4) not sell, trade, or transfer your Innovation Enterprise account to another party; and (5) not charge anyone for access to any portion of Innovation Enterprise, or any information therein. Further, you are responsible for anything that happens through your account until you close down your account or prove that your account security was compromised due to no fault of your own.

2.5. Indemnification

You will pay us for any losses that you cause.

You agree to indemnify us and hold us harmless for all damages, losses and costs (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs) related to all third party claims, charges, and investigations, caused by (1) your failure to comply with this Agreement, including, without limitation, your submission of content that violates third party rights or applicable laws, (2) any content you submit to the Services, and (3) any activity in which you engage on or through Innovation Enterprise.

2.6. Payment

You will honor your payment obligations and you are okay with us storing your payment information. Also, there may be fees and taxes that are added to our prices.

We don't guarantee refunds.

If you purchase any services that we offer for a fee, either on a one-time or subscription basis (“ieOnDemand”), you agree to Innovation Enterprise storing your payment information. You also agree to pay the applicable fees for the ieOnDemand Services (including, without limitation, periodic fees for ieOnDemand accounts) as they become due plus all related taxes, and to reimburse us for all collection costs and interest for any overdue amounts. Failure to pay may result in the termination of your subscription. Depending on where you transact with us, the type of payment method used and where your payment method was issued, your transaction with us may be subject to foreign exchange fees or differences in prices, including because of exchange rates. Innovation Enterprise does not support all payment methods, currencies or locations for payment. If the payment method you use with us, such as a credit card, reaches its expiration date and you do not edit your payment method information or cancel your account or such ieOnDemand Service, you authorize us to continue billing that payment method and you remain responsible for any uncollected amounts. Your obligation to pay fees continues through the end of the subscription period during which you cancel your subscription. All applicable taxes are calculated based on the billing information you provide us at the time of purchase. You may cancel or suspend your ieOnDemand Services here. Innovation Enterprise’s refund policy is explained [here](https://ieondemand.com/refund_policy). We do not guarantee refunds for lack of usage or dissatisfaction. You also acknowledge that Innovation Enterprise’s ieOnDemand Services are subject to this Agreement and any additional terms related to the provision of the ieOnDemand Service. Additionally, if you require a printed invoice for your transaction with us, you may access it through your Innovation Enterprise account settings under “Dashboard” or, request one by contacting[cgomez@theiegroup.com](mailto:cgomez@theiegroup.com)

2.7. Notify us of acts contrary to the Agreement

If you think you have to breach this Agreement, you will let us know beforehand.

If you believe that you are entitled or obligated to act contrary to this Agreement under any mandatory law, you agree to provide us with detailed and substantiated explanation of your reasons in writing at least 30 days before you act contrary to this Agreement, to allow us to assess whether we may, at our sole discretion, provide an alternative remedy for the situation, though we are under no obligation to do so.

2.8. Notifications and Service Messages

You are okay with us providing you with important notices on our websites, mobile apps, or email.

The contact information you provide must be accurate or you may not receive important notices.

Notice may consist of an email from Innovation Enterprise to an email address associated with your account, even if we have other contact information. You also agree that Innovation Enterprise may communicate with you through your Innovation Enterprise account or through other means including email, mobile number, telephone, or delivery services including the postal service about your Innovation Enterprise account or services associated with Innovation Enterprise. Please review your Innovation [Enterprise.com](http://enterprise.com/) and [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/), or subscription centre settings to control and limit what kind of messages you receive from us. You acknowledge and agree that we shall have no liability associated with or arising from your failure to do so maintain accurate contact or other information, including, but not limited to, your failure to receive critical information about the Services.

2.9. Innovation Enterprise Applications

This Agreement applies to mobile applications as well. Also, you agree certain additional information can be shared with us.

Innovation Enterprise may offer the Services through applications. If you use a Innovation Enterprise Application or interact with a website that has deployed a plugin, you agree that information about you and your use of the Services, including, but not limited to, your device, your mobile carrier, your internet access provider, your physical location, or web pages containing Innovation Enterprise plugins that load in your browser may be communicated to us. Further, by importing any of your Innovation Enterprise data through the Innovation Enterprise Application, you represent that you have authority to share the transferred data with your mobile carrier or other access provider. You acknowledge you are responsible for all charges and necessary permissions related to accessing Innovation Enterprise through your mobile access provider. Therefore, you should check with your provider to find out if the Services are available and the terms for these services for your specific mobile devices. Finally, by using any downloadable application to enable your use of the Services, you are explicitly confirming your acceptance of the terms of the End User License Agreement associated with the application provided at download or installation, or as may be updated from time to time.

2.10. User-to-User Communication and Sharing (Innovation Enterprise Channels, etc.)

When you share information, others can see, copy and use that information.

Innovation Enterprise offers various forums such [ieodndemand.com](http://ieodndemand.com/) where you can post your observations and comments on designated topics. Innovation Enterprise also enables sharing of information by allowing users to post updates, including links to news articles and other information such as job opportunities, product recommendations, and other content to their profile and other Services, such as [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/), Innovation Enterprise Channels and Innovation Enterprise Company Pages. Innovation Enterprise members can create content & articles for free, however, Innovation Enterprise, in its sole discretion, may remove content from them or from anywhere on the Services if the content violates this Agreement or others’ intellectual property rights. Please note that ideas you post and information you share may be seen and used by other Members or, if public, by Visitors (note also that all content you post on [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/) is publicly visible and Innovation Enterprise cannot guarantee that other Members will or will not use the ideas and information that you share on Innovation Enterprise, nor the manner of use. Therefore, if you have an idea or information that you would like to keep confidential or don’t want others to use, or that is subject to third party rights that may be infringed by your sharing it, do not post it to any Innovation Enterprise channels, into yor elsewhere on Innovation Enterprise & [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/). Innovation Enterprise IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANOTHER’S MISUSE OR MISAPPROPRIATION OF ANY CONTENT OR INFORMATION YOU POST ON Innovation Enterprise or [ieondemand.com](http://ieondemand.com/).

2.11. Privacy

You are okay with us collecting, using, storing, and disclosing information about you in keeping with our [Privacy Policy](https://ieondemand.com/privacy_policy).

You should carefully read our full [Privacy Policy](https://ieondemand.com/privacy_policy) before using Innovation Enterprise as it is hereby incorporated into this Agreement by reference, and governs our treatment of any information, including personally identifiable information you submit to us. Please note that certain information, statements, data, and content (such as photographs) which you may submit to Innovation Enterprise reveal your gender, ethnic origin, nationality, age, and/or other personal information about you. You acknowledge that your submission of any information, statements, data, and content to us is voluntary on your part and that Innovation Enterprise may process such information, within the terms of the Privacy Policy.

2.12. Contributions to Innovation Enterprise

If you provide content to us, make sure you don’t include confidential or infringing materials. You grant us rights to your content.

By submitting suggestions or other contnent regarding in any way to Innovation Enterprise, you acknowledge and agree that: (a) your Contributions do not contain confidential or proprietary information; (b) Innovation Enterprise is not under any obligation of confidentiality, express or implied, with respect to the Contributions; (c) Innovation Enterprise shall be entitled to use or disclose (or choose not to use or disclose) such Contributions for any purpose, in any way, in any media worldwide; (d) Innovation Enterprise may have something similar to the Contributions already under consideration or in development; (e) you irrevocably non-exclusively license to Innovation Enterprise rights to exploit your Contributions; and (f) you are not entitled to any compensation or reimbursement of any kind from Innovation Enterprise under any circumstances.

3\. Your Rights

If you follow this agreement, we grant you a limited right to use Innovation Enterprise.

You will only access and use Innovation Enterprise in the way this agreement allows you.

On the condition that you comply with all your obligations under this Agreement, including, but not limited to, the Do’s and Don’ts listed in Section 10, we grant you a limited, revocable, nonexclusive, nonassignable, nonsublicenseable license and right to access the Services, through a generally available web browser, mobile device or Innovation Enterprise authorized application (but not through scraping, spidering, crawling or other technology or software used to access data without the express written consent of Innovation Enterprise or its Members), to view content and information and otherwise use the Services, to the extent intended and permitted by the functionality thereof, the Members’ settings and your degree of connection with them, in accordance with this Agreement. Any other use of Innovation Enterprise contrary to our mission and purpose (such as seeking to connect to someone you do not know or trust, or to use information gathered from Innovation Enterprise commercially unless expressly authorized by Innovation Enterprise) is strictly prohibited and a violation of this Agreement. We reserve all rights not expressly granted in this Agreement, including, without limitation, title, ownership, intellectual property rights, and all other rights and interest in Innovation Enterprise and all related items, including any and all copies made of the Innovation Enterprise websites.

4\. Our Rights & Obligations

4.1. Services Availability

We may change or discontinue Services, and in such case, we do not promise to keep showing or storing your information and content.

For as long as Innovation Enterprise continues to offer the Services, Innovation Enterprise shall provide and seek to update, improve and expand the Services. As a result, we allow you to access Innovation Enterprise as it may exist and be available on any given day and we have no other obligations, except as expressly stated in this Agreement. We may modify, replace, refuse access to, suspend or discontinue Innovation Enterprise, partially or entirely, or change and modify prices prospectively for all or part of the Services for you or for all our Members in our sole discretion. All of these changes shall be effective upon their posting on Innovation Enterprise or by direct communication to you unless otherwise noted.

We may not keep showing the content or information you provide to us.

Innovation Enterprise further reserves the right to withhold, remove or discard any content available as part of your account, with or without notice if deemed by Innovation Enterprise to be contrary to this Agreement. For avoidance of doubt, Innovation Enterprise has no obligation to store, maintain or provide you a copy of any content that you or other Members provide when using the Services. Innovation Enterprise may be required by local laws to remove certain information or content and so that information or content may not be available on our Service in those countries.

4.2. Third Party Content & Sites

Your access of other Members’ and third parties’ content and information posted on the Services is at your own risk.

By using the Services, you may be exposed to other Members’ or third party content or information that might be inaccurate, incomplete, delayed, misleading, illegal, offensive or otherwise harmful. Except for certain limited circumstances, such as where legally required, we generally do not review or filter such content. You agree and acknowledge that we are not responsible for other Members’ or third party content or information or for any damage of any kind incurred as result of your reliance thereon.

Third parties may offer their own products and services through Innovation Enterprise, and we are not responsible for these third-party activities.

4.3. Disclosure of User Information

You agree that we can use, store, and share information about you as permitted in our [Privacy Policy](https://ieondemand.com/privacy_policy).

You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose your registration and any other information you provide in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary in our opinion to: (1) comply with legal process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other compulsory disclosures; (2) enforce this Agreement; (3) respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties, whether or not the third party is a Member, individual, or government agency; (4) respond to customer service inquiries;

4.4. Intellectual Property Notices

We are providing you notice about our intellectual property rights.

The Services include the copyrights and Intellectual property rights of Innovation Enterprise and except for the limited license granted to you in Section 3, Innovation Enterprise reserves all of its intellectual property rights in the Services. Innovation Enterprise, ieOnDemand logos and other Innovation Enterprise trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos used in connection with Innovation Enterprise are trademarks or registered trademarks of Innovation Enterprise or ieOnDemand. This Agreement does not grant you any right or license with respect to any such trademarks and logos.

5\. Disclaimer

We disclaim any legal liability for the quality, safety, or reliability of Innovation Enterprise.

SOME COUNTRIES AND JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OF IMPLIED TERMS IN CONTRACTS WITH CONSUMERS AND AS A RESULT THE CONTENTS OF THIS SECTION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. DO NOT RELY ON Innovation Enterprise OR ITS SUPPLIERS, ANY INFORMATION THEREIN, OR ITS CONTINUATION. WE PROVIDE THE PLATFORM FOR Innovation Enterprise AND ALL INFORMATION AND SERVICES ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. Innovation Enterprise DOES NOT CONTROL OR VET USER GENERATED CONTENT FOR ACCURACY. WE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY EXPRESS WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, Innovation Enterprise AND ITS SUPPLIERS DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, ACCURACY OF DATA, AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED OR HARMED BY Innovation Enterprise OR ANYTHING RELATED TO Innovation Enterprise, YOU MAY CLOSE YOUR Innovation Enterprise ACCOUNT AND TERMINATE THIS AGREEMENT IN ACCORDANCE WITH SECTION 7 (“TERMINATION”) AND SUCH TERMINATION SHALL BE YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY. Innovation Enterprise IS NOT RESPONSIBLE, AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES FOR THE DELIVERY OF ANY MESSAGES (SUCH AS INMAILS, POSTING OF ANSWERS OR TRANSMISSION OF ANY OTHER USER GENERATED CONTENT) SENT THROUGH Innovation Enterprise TO ANYONE. IN ADDITION, WE NEITHER WARRANT NOR REPRESENT THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL NOT INFRINGE THE RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES. ANY MATERIAL, SERVICE, OR TECHNOLOGY DESCRIBED OR USED ON OUR WEBSITES MAY BE SUBJECT TO INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS OWNED BY THIRD PARTIES WHO HAVE LICENSED SUCH MATERIAL, SERVICE, OR TECHNOLOGY TO US. Innovation Enterprise DOES NOT HAVE ANY OBLIGATION TO VERIFY THE IDENTITY OF THE PERSONS SUBSCRIBING TO ITS SERVICES, NOR DOES IT HAVE ANY OBLIGATION TO MONITOR THE USE OF ITS SERVICES BY OTHER USERS OF THE COMMUNITY; THEREFORE, Innovation Enterprise DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR IDENTITY THEFT OR ANY OTHER MISUSE OF YOUR IDENTITY OR INFORMATION BY OTHERS. Innovation Enterprise DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE SERVICES IT PROVIDES WILL FUNCTION WITHOUT INTERRUPTION OR ERRORS IN FUNCTIONING. IN PARTICULAR, THE OPERATION OF THE SERVICES MAY BE INTERRUPTED DUE TO MAINTENANCE, UPDATES, OR SYSTEM OR NETWORK FAILURES. Innovation Enterprise DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES CAUSED BY ANY SUCH INTERRUPTION OR ERRORS IN FUNCTIONING. FURTHERMORE, Innovation Enterprise DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR ANY MALFUNCTIONING, IMPOSSIBILITY OF ACCESS, OR POOR USE CONDITIONS OF THE Innovation Enterprise SITES DUE TO INAPPROPRIATE EQUIPMENT, DISTURBANCES RELATED TO INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDERS, TO THE SATURATION OF THE INTERNET NETWORK, AND FOR ANY OTHER REASON.

6\. Limitation of Liability

We are trying to limit any legal liability we may have to you.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. SOME COUNTRIES DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY IN CONTRACTS WITH CONSUMERS AND AS A RESULT THE CONTENTS OF THIS SECTION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. Neither Innovation Enterprise nor any of our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, suppliers, employees, shareholders, or directors (“Innovation Enterprise Affiliates”) shall be cumulatively liable for (a) any damages in excess of five times the most recent monthly fee that you paid for a Service, if any, or US $69, whichever amount is greater, or (b) any special, incidental, indirect, punitive or consequential damages or loss of use, profit, revenue or data to you or any third person arising from your use of the Services, any Platform Applications or any of the content or other materials on, accessed through or downloaded from Innovation Enterprise. This limitation of liability is part of the basis of the bargain between the parties and without it the terms and prices charged would be different. This limitation of liability shall:

Apply regardless of whether (1) you base your claim on contract, tort, statute or any other legal theory, (2) we knew or should have known about the possibility of such damages, or (3) the limited remedies provided in this section fail of their essential purpose; and

Not apply to any damage that Innovation Enterprise may cause you intentionally or knowingly in violation of this Agreement or applicable law, or as otherwise mandated by applicable law that cannot be disclaimed in this Agreement.

Not apply if you have entered into a separate agreement to purchase ieondemand Services with a separate Limitation of Liability provision that supersedes this section in relation to those ieOnDemand Services.

7\. Termination

7.1. Mutual rights of termination

We can each end this Agreement anytime we want.

You may terminate this Agreement, for any or no reason, at any time, with notice to Innovation Enterprise pursuant to Section 9.3. This notice will be effective upon Innovation Enterprise processing your notice. Innovation Enterprise may terminate this Agreement and your account for any reason or no reason, at any time, with or without notice. This cancellation shall be effective immediately or as may be specified in the notice. For avoidance of doubt, only Innovation Enterprise or the party paying for the services may terminate your access to any ieondemand Services. Termination of your Innovation Enterprise account includes disabling your access to Innovation Enterprise and may also bar you from any future use of Innovation Enterprise.

7.2. Misuse of the Services

Innovation Enterprise may restrict, suspend or terminate the account of any user who abuses or misuses the Services. Misuse of the Services includes inviting other users with whom you do not know to connect; abusing the Innovation Enterprise services; creating multiple or false profiles; using the Services commercially without Innovation Enterprise’s authorization, infringing any intellectual property rights, violating any of the Do’s and Don’ts listed in Section 10, or any other behavior that Innovation Enterprise, in its sole discretion, deems contrary to its purpose. In addition, and without limiting the foregoing, Innovation Enterprise has adopted a policy of terminating accounts of Members who, in Innovation Enterprise’s sole discretion, are deemed to be repeat infringers under the United States Copyright Act.

7.3. Effect of Termination

Upon termination of your Innovation Enterprise account, you lose access to the Services. The terms of this Agreement shall survive any termination, except Section 3 (“Your Rights”) and Sections 4.1., 4.2., and 4.3. (“Our Rights and Obligations”).

8\. Dispute Resolution

8.1. Law and Forum for Legal Disputes

This Agreement or any claim, cause of action or dispute (“claim”) arising out of or related to this Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the state of New york regardless of your country of origin or where you access Innovation Enterprise, and notwithstanding of any conflicts of law principles and the United Nations Convention for the International Sale of Goods. You and Innovation Enterprise agree that all claims arising out of or related to this Agreement must be resolved exclusively by a state or federal court located in New York, except as otherwise agreed by the parties or as described in the Arbitration Option paragraph below. You and Innovation Enterprise agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located within New York for the purpose of litigating all such claims. Notwithstanding the above, you agree that Innovation Enterprise shall still be allowed to apply for injunctive remedies (or an equivalent type of urgent legal relief) in any jurisdiction.

8.2. Arbitration Option

Each of us will have the right to choose arbitration.

9\. General Terms

9.1. Severability

Here are some important details about how to read the Agreement.

If any provision of this Agreement is found by a court of competent jurisdiction or arbitrator to be illegal, void, or unenforceable, the unenforceable provision will be modified so as to render it enforceable and effective to the maximum extent possible in order to effect the intention of the provision; if a court or arbitrator finds the modified provision invalid, illegal, void or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Agreement will not be affected in any way.

9.2. Language

Where Innovation Enterprise has provided you with a translation of the English language version of this Agreement, the Privacy Policy, or any other documentation, you agree that the translation is provided for your convenience only and that the English language versions of this Agreement, the Privacy Policy, and any other documentation, including additional terms of service for ieondemand Services, will govern your relationship with Innovation Enterprise.

9.3. Notices and Service of Process

In addition to Section 2.8.we may notify you via postings on [theinnovationenterprise.com](http://theinnovationenterprise.com/) or another Innovation Enterprise site or app. You may contact us here [info@theiegroup.com](mailto:info@theiegroup.com). Or via mail or courier at: Innovation Enterprise Additionally, Innovation Enterprise accepts service of process at this address 45 West 45th Street, 12th Floor, New York, NY. Any notices that you provide without compliance with this section shall have no legal effect.

9.4. Entire Agreement

You agree that this Agreement constitutes the entire, complete and exclusive agreement between you and Innovation Enterprise regarding the Services and supersedes all prior agreements and understandings, whether written or oral, or whether established by custom, practice, policy or precedent, with respect to the subject matter of this Agreement. You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use or purchase certain other Innovation Enterprise services, third-party content or third party software.

9.5. Amendments to This Agreement

We reserve the right to modify, supplement, or replace the terms of this Agreement, effective prospectively upon posting at www.Innovation [Enterprise.com](http://enterprise.com/) or notifying you otherwise. For example, we may present a banner on the Services when we have amended this Agreement or the Privacy Policy so that you may access and review the changes prior to your continued use of the Services. If you do not want to agree to changes to this Agreement, you can terminate this Agreement at any time per Section 7 (Termination).

9.6. No informal waivers, agreements or representations

Our failure to act with respect to a breach of this Agreement by you or others does not waive our right to act with respect to that breach or subsequent similar or other breaches. Except as expressly and specifically contemplated by the Agreement, no representations, statements, consents, waivers or other acts or omissions by any Innovation Enterprise Affiliate shall be deemed legally binding on any Innovation Enterprise Affiliate, unless documented in a physical writing hand signed by a duly appointed officer of Innovation Enterprise.

9.7. No Injunctive Relief

You waive your rights to try to stop Innovation Enterprise, but we don’t waive our rights to ask a court to stop your actions.

In no event shall you seek or be entitled to rescission, injunctive or other equitable relief, or to enjoin or restrain the operation of the Services, exploitation of any advertising or other materials issued in connection therewith, or exploitation of the Services or any content or other material used or displayed through the Services.

9.8. Assignment and Delegation

You can’t assign your rights under this Agreement, but we can.

You may not assign or delegate any rights or obligations under the Agreement. Any purported assignment and delegation shall be ineffective. We may freely assign or delegate all rights and obligations under the Agreement, fully or partially without notice to you. We may also substitute, by way of unilateral novation, effective upon notice to you, Innovation Enterprise for any third party that assumes our rights and obligations under this Agreement.

9.9. Potential Other Rights and Obligations

You may have rights or obligations under local law other than those enumerated here if you are located outside the United States.

10\. Innovation Enterprise “DOs” and “DON’Ts.”

As a condition to access Innovation Enterprise, you agree to this User Agreement and to strictly observe the following DOs and DON’Ts:

10.1. Do undertake the following:

Here’s a list of some of the specific things we ask you to do and not do on Innovation Enterprise.

Comply with all applicable laws, including, without limitation, privacy laws, intellectual property laws, export control laws, tax laws, and regulatory requirements;

Provide accurate information to us and update it as necessary;

Review and comply with our [Privacy Policy](https://ieondemand.com/privacy_policy);

Review and comply with notices sent by Innovation Enterprise concerning the ieOnDemand Services;

Use the ieOnDemand Services in a professional manner; and

Use your real name on your profile.

10.2. Don’t undertake the following:

Act dishonestly or unprofessionally by engaging in unprofessional behavior by posting inappropriate, inaccurate, or objectionable content to Innovation Enterprise;

Publish inaccurate information in the designated fields on the profile for.

Create a Member profile for anyone other than a natural person;

Harass, abuse or harm another person, including sending unwelcome comments to others using Innovation Enterprise;

Use or attempt to use another's account or create a false identity on Innovation Enterprise;

Is unlawful, libelous, abusive, obscene, discriminatory or otherwise objectionable;

Infringes upon patents, trademarks, trade secrets, copyrights or other proprietary rights;

Includes any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, “junk mail,” “spam,” “chain letters,” “pyramid schemes,” or any other form of solicitation.

Duplicate, license, sublicense, publish, broadcast, transmit, distribute, perform, display, sell, rebrand, or otherwise transfer information found on Innovation Enterprise (excluding content posted by you) except as permitted in this Agreement;

Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, decipher or otherwise attempt to derive the source code for any underlying intellectual property used to provide the Services, or any part thereof;

Utilize or copy information, content or any data you view on or obtain from Innovation Enterprise to provide any service that is competitive, in Innovation Enterprise’s sole discretion, with Innovation Enterprise;

Imply or state, directly or indirectly, that you are affiliated with or endorsed by Innovation Enterprise unless you have entered into a written agreement with Innovation Enterprise (this includes, but is not limited to, representing yourself as an accredited Innovation Enterprise Advisory Board if you have not been certified by Innovation Enterprise as such);

Rent, lease, loan, trade, sell/re-sell access to Innovation Enterprise or any information therein, or the equivalent, in whole or part;

Infringe or use Innovation Enterprise’s brand, logos or trademarks, including, without limitation, using the word “Innovation Enterprise” or ‘ieOnDemand' in any business name, email, or URL or including Innovation Enterprise’s trademarks and logos except as provided in the Brand Guidelines or as expressly permitted by Innovation Enterprise;

Engage in “framing,” “mirroring,” or otherwise simulating the appearance or function of Innovation Enterprise’s website;

Attempt to or actually override any security component included in or underlying Innovation Enterprise;

Interfere or disrupt or game Innovation Enterprise or the Services, including, but not limited to, any servers or networks connected to Innovation Enterprise,

11\. Complaints Regarding Content Posted on the Innovation Enterprise Website

If you think someone has stolen or misused your intellectual property on Innovation Enterprise, please check out our [Copyright Policy](https://ieondemand.com/copyright_policy).

We built Innovation Enterprise to help you get the professional information you need to improve, and to help professionals succeed. To achieving this purpose, we encourage our Members to share accurate information. We also respect the intellectual property rights of others. Accordingly, this Agreement requires that information posted authors be accurate and not in violation of the intellectual property rights or other rights of third parties. To promote these objectives, Innovation Enterprise provides a process for submission of complaints concerning content posted by our Members. Our policy and procedures can be found here: Innovation Enterprise Copyright Policy. Claims regarding Copyright Infringement. Claims regarding content (other than copyright).

How To Contact Us

If you have questions or comments about this User Agreement, please contact us online or by physical mail at:

For users in the United States:

Innovation Enterprise Attn: Agreement Issues

CFO Customer Service

45 West 45th Street, 12th Floor

New York, NY 10036

Phone: [](tel:212-459-3004)[212-459-3004](https://www.switch.co/launch?phone=212-459-3004 "Call with Switch.co")

\- See more at: <https://ieondemand.com/terms_of_service#sthash.TrKC1kYd.dpuf>
